{"question":"6 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"12", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"35", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"18", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"35", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"32", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"10", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"35", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"15", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"63", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"24", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"12", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"16", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"12", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"20", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"40", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"32", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"10", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"18", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"24", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"32", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"14", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"35", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"36", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"18", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"27", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"24", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"64", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"36", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"12", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"48", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"14", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"30", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"36", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"56", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"45", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"30", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"81", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"30", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"16", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"40", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"81", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"20", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"20", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"18", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"81", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"28", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"15", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"12", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"36", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"24", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"24", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"45", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"15", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"42", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"45", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"24", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"48", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"24", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"14", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"48", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"63", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"45", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"48", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"15", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"14", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"48", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"45", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"35", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"15", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"81", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"45", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"18", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"56", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"18", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"40", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"27", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"56", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"16", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"45", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"63", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"27", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"14", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"25", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"27", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"20", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"20", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"21", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"18", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"63", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"63", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"28", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"12", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"36", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"35", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"63", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"45", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"48", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"12", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"30", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"24", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"40", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"14", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"54", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"15", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"30", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"63", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"18", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"35", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"27", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"64", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"45", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"14", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"10", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"21", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"72", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"14", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"10", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"72", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"27", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"30", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"10", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"35", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"49", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"30", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"18", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"25", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"45", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"12", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"24", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"21", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"56", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"81", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"49", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"18", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"72", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"14", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"18", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"18", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"36", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"21", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"24", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"25", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"16", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"20", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"12", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"20", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"45", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"32", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"18", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"18", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"72", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
